karnatakaholidays.net 2019-09-25

# Privacy Policy – KSTDC Ltd.,

Privacy Policy – KSTDC Ltd.,
Introduction:
The Privacy Policy covers the practices for handling and securing your Personal Information by KSTDC
Ltd.,
This Privacy Policy is applicable to persons who purchase any product or services from KSTDC Ltd.,
through any Sales Channel of KSTDC Ltd., (like website, mobile site, mobile app & offline channels
including call centres and retail offices). This Privacy Policy also applies to persons who visit the KSTDC’s
offices or Sales Channels.
As a user or customer of KSTDC Ltd.,, the person agrees with this Privacy Policy and the terms and
conditions mentioned herein.
This privacy statement does not apply to the websites, mobile sites and mobile apps of our other third
parties, even if their websites are linked to KSTDC Ltd., Website. We recommend you review the privacy
statements of the other parties with whom you interact.
What Personal Information we collect from you and how we use it?
‘Personal Information’ means and includes all information that can be linked to a specific individual or to
identify any individual, such as name, address, mailing address, telephone number, email address, credit
card number, cardholder name, expiration date, information about the travel, bookings, passengers,
frequent traveller / flier numbers, and any and all details that may be necessary from the customer.
When you visit KSTDC website, we may collect information regarding the domain and host from which
you access the internet, the internet protocol address of the computer or internet service provider you are
using, and anonymous statistical data. The website and mobile site uses cookie and tracking technology
depending on the features offered. Personal Information will not be collected via cookies and other
tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may
be tied to such information.
When browsing our Website, you are not required to provide any Personal Information unless and until
you choose to make a purchase or sign up for one of our e-mail newsletters or other services as described
below.
Making a Purchase
In order to purchase travel and/or related services through our Website, you must provide us with certain
Personal Information such as your name, credit card number and expiration date, credit card billing
address, telephone number, e - mail address and the name or names of the person(s) traveling (if not
you). We require this information to process, fulfill and confirm your reservations and transactions and
keep you informed of each transaction's status. If you are making a reservation for one or more travelers
other than yourself, you must confirm and represent that each of these other travelers have agreed, in
advance, that you may disclose their Personal Information to us.
Member Registration

If you choose to become a registered member of Website, you must provide your name, address,
telephone number, e-mail address, a unique login name, password, and password validation, and a
password hint to help you remember your password. This information is collected on the registration form
for several reasons including but not limited to:
       1.Personal identification
       2.To complete the travel and stay reservations
       3.To allow us to contact you for customer service purposes, if necessary
       4.To customize the content of our website, mobile site and mobile app to strive to meet your
       specific needs; and
       5.To make product or other improvements;
       6.To confirm your new member registration and each reservation you make.
Member Profile:
As a member, you can choose to complete your online profile by providing us with travel preferences,
frequent - traveller or affinity numbers, credit card billing information, paper ticket delivery address, and
other Personal Information. This information is primarily used to assist you in making reservations quickly
without having to type in the same information repeatedly.
Surveys:
KSTDC Ltd., values opinions and comments from members, so we frequently conduct surveys, both online
and offline. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically, the information is aggregated, and
used to make improvements to website, mobile site and mobile app and its services and to develop
appealing content, features and promotions for members. Survey participants are anonymous unless
otherwise stated in the survey.
Promotions & Sweepstakes:
KSTDC Ltd., frequently sponsors promotions and sweepstakes to give members the opportunity to win
great travel and travel - related prizes. Information collected by us for such activities may include contact
information and survey questions. We use contact information to notify contest winners and survey
information to develop promotions and product improvements. As a member you will also occasionally
receive updates from us about fare sales in your area, special offers, new KSTDC Ltd., services, and other
noteworthy items (like savings and benefits hotel reservations, holiday packages, car rentals and other
travel services). In addition, you may look forward to receiving monthly newsletters and exclusive
promotions offering special deals. However, you may choose at any time to no longer receive these types
of e - mail messages.
Automatic Logging of Session Data:
We automatically log generic information about your devices connection to the Internet, which we call
"session data", that is anonymous and not linked to any Personal Information. Session data consists of
things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities
conducted by the user while on the device. An IP address is a number that lets devices attached to the
internet, such as our web servers, know where to send data back to the user, such as the pages of the
website the user wishes to view. We collect session data because it helps us analyse such things as what
items visitors are likely to click on most, the way visitors are clicking through the website/ mobile site/
mobile app, how many visitors are surfing to various pages on the website/ mobile site/ mobile app, how
long visitors are staying and how often they are visiting. It also helps us diagnose problems with our

servers and lets us better administer our systems. Although such information does not identify any visitor
personally, it is possible to determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider (ISP), and the
approximate geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your device's hard drive.
Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to do such things as run programs
on your computer, plant viruses or harvest your Personal Information. The use of cookies is very common
on the Internet.
KSTDC use of cookies is similar to that of any other reputable online companies. No personally identifiable
information (PII) about you (e.g., name, address, etc.) is gathered or stored in the cookies placed by a
website or mobile site and, as a result, none can be passed on to any third parties. Cookies allow us to
serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our website and mobile site.
KSTDC Ltd., uses cookies to personalize your experience on the website and mobile site, and with respect
to advertisements.
As to the personalization of experience, these types of cookies allow you to log in without having to type
your log - in name each time (only your password is needed); we may also use such cookies to display an
advertisement to you while you are on the Website or mobile site or to send you a ‘best day to buy email
(or similar emails - assuming you have not opted out of receiving such emails) focusing on destinations in
which we think you might be interested. None of this information is passed to any third party, and is used
solely by us to provide you with a better user experience on the Website and mobile site.
A cookie may also be placed by our advertising server. Such cookies are used only for purposes of
tracking the effectiveness of advertising served by us on our website and mobile site and no PII is
gathered from you by the use of these cookies, nor is this information shared with any third parties.
Similarly, a cookie may be placed by our third - party advertising companies or advertisement providers or
servers. These companies may use aggregated statistics about your visits to our websites or mobile sites
in order to provide advertisements about travel - related goods and services that you may be interested in
or any goods and services of potential interest to you. The information they collect does not include your
PII.
The third - party advertising companies or advertisement providers may also employ technology that is
used to measure the effectiveness of ads. Any such information is anonymous. They may use this
anonymous information about your visits to our websites in order to provide advertisements about goods
and services of potential interest to you. No PII is collected during this process. The information is
anonymous, and does not link online actions to an identifiable person.
Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. Of course, by changing the options on your web
browser or using certain software programs, you can control how and whether cookies will be accepted
by your browser. KSTDC Ltd., supports your right to block any unwanted Internet activity, especially that
of unscrupulous websites. However, blocking KSTDC Ltd., cookies may disable certain features on the
website and mobile site, and may make it impossible to purchase or use certain services available on the
website and mobile site. Please note that it is possible to block cookie activity from certain websites while
permitting cookies from websites you trust.
Others:

From time to time we may add or enhance services available on the Website. To the extent these services
are provided, and used by you, we will use the information you provide to facilitate the service requested.
For example, if you email us with a question, we will use your email address, name, nature of the question,
etc. to respond to your question. We may also store such information to assist us in making the Website
the better and easier to use.
With whom your Personal Information is shared?
When you reserve or purchase travel services through us, we must provide certain of your Personal
Information to the hotel, car - rental agency, travel agency or other involved third party to enable the
successful fulfillment of your travel arrangements.
However, we do not sell or rent individual customer names or other Personal Information to third parties
except sharing of such information with our alliance partners or vendors who are engaged by us for
providing various promotional and other benefits to our customers from time to time basis their booking
history with us.
We may also share certain filtered Personal Information to our business partners who may contact the
customers to offer certain products or services (which may include free or paid products / services) which
will enable the customer to have better travel experience or to avail certain benefits specially made for
KSTDC Ltd., Customers. Examples of such partners are entities offering co-branded credit cards, travel
insurance, insurance cover against loss of wallet, banking cards or similar sensitive information etc.
We use non - personally identifiable information in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful
online services by performing statistical analysis of the collective characteristics and behavior of our
customers and visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the
website, mobile site and mobile app. We may provide anonymous statistical information based on this
data to suppliers, advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential Business partners. We may also use
such aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked
on links to their websites.
Occasionally, KSTDC Ltd., will hire a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as market - research
surveys and contest - entry processing and will provide information to these third parties specifically for
use in connection with these projects. The information (including aggregate cookie and tracking
information) we provide to such third parties, alliance partners, or vendors are protected by confidentiality
agreements and such information is to be used solely for completing the specific project, and in
compliance with the applicable regulations.
How you can opt-out of receiving our promotional e-mails?
At any time, you may unsubscribe from our newsletters or promotional services through the "My Account"
link on the website or mobile site or mobile app.
You will occasionally receive e-mail updates from us about fare sales in your area, special offers, new
KSTDC Ltd., services, and other noteworthy items. We hope you will find these updates interesting and
informative. If you wish not to receive them, please click on the "unsubscribe" link or follow the
instructions in each e - mail message or send us an email unsubscribe@karnatakaholidays.net.
KSTDC Ltd., reserves the right to limit membership to those who will accept e - mails.
What safeguards we have in place to protect your Personal Information?

All payments on the website, mobile site and mobile app are secured.
This means all Personal Information you provide is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer)
encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data
before you send it to us.
What Android and iOS Permissions required while using our mobile applications
When KSTDC Ltd., app is installed on your phone, a list of permissions appears. Since there is no option to
customize those permissions, below is a description of the permissions that KSTDC Ltd., requires and the
data that KSTDC Ltd., shall access and use.
Android permissions:
Device & App history: We need your device permission to get information about your device, like OS
(operating system) name, OS version, mobile network, hardware model, unique device identifier, preferred
language, etc. Basis these inputs, we intend to optimize your travel booking experience, use OS specific
capabilities to drive great in-funnel experiences using components of device’s OS, etc.
Identity: This permission enables us to know about details of your account(s) on your mobile device. We
use this info to auto-fill your email ID’s and provide a typing free in-funnel experience. It helps us map
email ID’s to a particular user to give you the benefit of exclusive travel offers, wallet cash-backs, etc. It
also allows facilitating your Facebook and Google+ login.
Location: This permission enables us to give you the benefit of location specific deals and provide you a
personalized in-funnel experience. When you launch KSTDC Ltd., app to make a travel booking, we auto-
detect your location so that your nearest airport or city is auto-filled. We also require this permission to
recommend you nearest hotels in case you are running late and want to make a quick last minute
booking for the nearest hotel. Your options are personalized basis your locations. For international travel,
this enables us to determine your time zone and provide information accordingly.
SMS: If you allow us to access your SMS, we read your SMS to autofill or prepopulate ‘OTP’ while making
a transaction and to validate your mobile number. This provides you a seamless purchase experience
while making a booking and you don’t need to move out of the app to read the SMS and then enter it in
the app.
Phone: The app requires access to make phone calls so that you can make phone calls to hotels and our
customer contact centers directly through the app.
Contacts: If you allow us to access your contacts, it enables us to provide a lot of social features to you
such as sharing your hotel/ flight/ holidays with your friends, inviting your friends to try our app, send
across referral links to your friends, etc. We will also use this information to make recommendations for
hotels where your friends have stayed. This information will be stored on our servers and synced from
your phone.
Photo/ Media/ Files: The libraries in the app use these permissions to allow map data to be saved to your
phone's external storage, like SD cards. By saving map data locally, your phone doesn't need to re-
download the same map data every time you use the app. This provides you a seamless Map based Hotel
selection experience, even on low bandwidth network.

Wi-Fi connection information: When you allow us the permission to detect your Wi-Fi connection, we
optimize your experience such as more detailing on maps, better image loading, more hotel/ flights/
package options to choose from, etc.
Device ID & Call information: This permission is used to detect your Android ID through which we can
uniquely identify users. It also lets us know your contact details using which we pre-populate specific
fields to ensure a seamless booking experience.
Calendar: This permission enables us to put your travel plan on your calendar.
iOS Permissions:
Notifications: If you opt in for notifications, it enables us to send across exclusive deals, promotional
offers, travel related updates, etc. on your device. If you do not opt for this, updates for your travel like
PNR status, booking confirmation, refund (in case of cancellation), etc. will be sent through SMS.
Contacts: If you opt in for contacts permission, it enables us to provide a lot of social features to you such
as sharing your hotel/ flight/ holidays with your friends, inviting your friends to try our app, send across
referral links to your friends, etc. We will also use this information to make recommendations for hotels
where your friends have stayed. This information will be stored on our servers and synced from your
phone.
Location: This permission enables us to give you the benefit of location specific deals and provide you a
personalized in-funnel experience. When you launch our app to make a travel booking, we auto-detect
your location so that your nearest Airport or City is auto-filled. We require this permission to recommend
your nearest hotels in case you are running late and want to make a quick last minute booking for the
nearest hotel. Your options are personalized basis your locations. For international travel, this enables us
to determine your time zone and provide information accordingly.
What other information should I know about my privacy?
   Website, mobile site and mobile app contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on
one of these links, you are entering another website for which KSTDC Ltd., has no responsibility. We
encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different
from this Privacy Policy. Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your
passwords, and your membership account information. Please be very careful, responsible, and alert with
this information, especially whenever you're online.
In addition to the circumstances described above, KSTDC Ltd., may disclose the member information if
required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or
in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to
protect the rights or properties of KSTDC Ltd., or any or all of its affiliates, associates, employees, directors
or officers or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify,
contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or
properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. In
addition, if KSTDC Ltd., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, our customer information will most
likely also be transferred in connection with such acquisition.

We review our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we may make periodic changes to the policy in
connection with that review. Therefore, you may wish to bookmark this page and/or periodically review
this page to make sure you have the latest version.
You     may    always    submit    concerns      regarding this    Privacy  Policy   via    email   to
systemadmin@karnatakaholidays.net KSTDC Ltd., will respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries.
Thank you for using the Website!
